But I want to add this one that I just uploaded so I click on it and by clicking it will be added as you see
You know as easy as that and as you see we have
Plenty of options when it comes to designing so we can scale this image very easily
You know the interface is a very easy to work with interface. We can rotate as you see
we can crop
By clicking here. We can go to adjustments and we have brightness contrast and other
Properties of this image that we can control as you see
So we have plenty of options
We can
Click on auto enhance, you know, we can erase
so
Select the brush or draw a box around an object to edit
I wait a little bit
until the eraser
Is on
Yes, so as you see
We have select so how can we select?
This uses of one AI credit
Yes, what else do we have we have brush?
So
Yes using this brush this
brush eraser
I'll be able to click and drag
And that certain part of my image will be erased, right?
No, I need to come here and click on erase and then it will be erased
And this also uses one AI credit so it's very weird because I haven't done I have not done anything with AI
But this eraser tool
I just used the brush you know what I'm saying
But this eraser tool wants to remove another credit out of my 14 credits
So I don't want that but by clicking on erase it will work
It will eventually work, you know
So I come back to
Where we were over here
What else do we have?
We have a transparency position
And we can replace so by clicking on this one
I will be able to choose another image to replace this image of mine